好了  丽芙和玛蒂很快就要考完驾照回家了
Okay, Liv and Maddie will be back from their driving test any second.
准备好庆祝仪式了么
Ready to celebrate?
来看看
Check it.
放声高唱
Sing it loud!
（威斯康星州机动车驾驶执照）
哈  怎样
Bam! What?!
（驾照持有人 丽芙·鲁尼 玛蒂·鲁尼）
我简直等不及我拿到驾照
Ooh, I can't wait to get my license
能随心所欲开车去任何地方的那一刻了
and be able to go wherever I want.
当然在市域范围内
Within the city limits.
在爸妈不准我出门之前
Before my curfew.
开的还是个闻起来像乔伊臭脚的破面包车
In a beat-up minivan that smells like Joey's feet.
还是无比自由啊
Still freedom.
万岁
Whoo-hoo!
这叫自由
Freedom?
这是失去自由好不好
Try loss of freedom.
谁会在无比烦躁还想发短信发到大拇指抽筋
Who wants to drive when you can sit shotgun
的时候专心开车啊
and text until your thumbs fall off?
肯定不是我
Not me.
我真为玛蒂兴奋  拿到了驾照
I'm stoked for Maddie. Having a license...
意味着她可以去任何地方干任何事了
that means she can go anywhere and do anything.
像她这么负责任的青少年一定会
That a responsible teenager would do
先在严父这里得到批准
after getting approval from her father.
我怎么会让她不得到您的恩准就胡作非为呢
Not that I've ever asked her not to get approval.
为什么我还在滔滔不绝呢
Why am I still talking?
为什么你在我房子里呢
Why are you in my house?
为什么你不去理个发呢
Why haven't you gotten a haircut?
我们的问题都不少啊
We've all got questions.
她来了
There she is.
祝贺了  丽芙
Congratulations, Liv.
咱们的两个新司机之一
One of our two new drivers.
先别急着喝彩
Yes. Hold your rah-rahs.
我们中只有一个过了考试
Only one of us passed.
真是倒霉催了啊
Total bummer-rang.
啊  你下次就会拿到驾照了  孩子
Aw, you'll get it next time, kid.
不  我才是过了考试的那个
No. I'm the one who passed.
激动人心吧
License to surprise!
等等  如果你过了  就说明玛蒂没过考试
Wait, if you passed, that means Maddie failed.
玛蒂从来没考过不及格
Maddie doesn't fail anything.
- 哦  - 噢
- Ooh! - Oh!
快烧了  全都烧了
Burn it! Burn it all!
好吧
Well...
我没及格
I failed.
想必我终于知道失败的滋味了
Guess I know what it feels like to be a loser now.
就是乔伊你特别熟悉的那种滋味
You know what I'm talking about, Joey.
哎呀  如果你拿到驾照了
Ouch! I would call that a drive-by...
也算是狗屎运吧
if you had your license.
到底发生了什么
So what happened?
我跟你讲发生了什么吧
I will tell you what happened.
车管所太歧视人了
The DMV discriminates.
（DMV：Department Of Motor Vehicles，车管所)
他们只把驾照发给能够
Yeah. They only give their licenses
完成左转弯的人
to people who can make left-hand turns.
如果你想把车往左开  这招确实有用
They do come in handy when you want to go left.
为啥你要自找没事地开到
Why would you purposefully turn
一堆乱糟糟的车流里而抵达你本需
into oncoming traffic when you can go up one block
右拐三次就能到的地方
and make three rights?
谁这么急着要驾照啊  对不
Who needs their license anyway, am I right?
我啊  我要我的驾照啊
I do! I need my license!
别担心  玛蒂  我会开车带你去你想去的地方的
Don't worry, Maddie. I'll drive you anywhere you want to go.
我怎么还叽里呱啦说个不停啊
Seriously, why am I still talking?
我怎么还站在这里啊
Why am I still here?
我马上去把头发理了
I'll go get my hair cut.
最好的朋友
Better in stereo
不同的朋友
b... b... better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
-  I'm up with the sunshine -  Let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
-  I lace up my high tops -  Oh no
扣篮  热热身
slam dunk, ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
-  I'm under the spotlight -  Holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
I'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go go go
你  我最好的朋友
you you, the other half of me me
学不来的朋友
the half I'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you you, the better half of me me
离不开的朋友
the half I'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
各位  我有个大好消息要宣布一下
Guys! I have something really exciting to say.
你能不能先闭嘴两个小时
How about you pause your piehole for two hours?
我们待会再聊
We'll get to you later.
我们都洗耳恭听了  丽芙
We're all listening, Liv.
很好
Okay.
今年夏天在威斯康星州
There is a major film
有一部大电影要进行拍摄
shooting in Wisconsin this summer,
我被提名参演一个主要角色
and I'm up for a big part.
真刺激  电影讲什么的
How exciting! What's it about?
大概是关于一群狼崽子在太空里的吧
It's based on some book about wolves in space.
《太空狼人》
"Space Werewolves!"
这是我最喜欢的漫画小说了
That is my favorite graphic novel.
不会吧
No way!
他们想让我饰演特里斯坦
They want me to play Tristan.
莫非是特里斯坦·莱肯
As in Tristan Lycanth?
对
Yeah.
那个英雄
The hero?
哈哈  特里斯坦是个男孩
Ha ha, but Tristan's a boy.
准确地说是半狼人半男孩
Technically half-boy, half-werewolf.
但他绝对不会是个女孩子
But he is definitely not a girl.
对  暂时还不是
Right. Not yet.
但是制片人看了我在《放声歌唱》里的表现
But the people making the movie saw my episode of Sing it Loud!
就是我在国际空间站里唱女高音
right where I dreamt that I was on an international space station
打碎了本要撞击地球的小行星
and I saved the earth by singing the high note
拯救了芸芸众生的那一集
that shattered the asteroid before it hit earth. Aah!
我太喜欢那集了
I love that episode.
真的吗 我觉得这里面逻辑错误不少啊
Really? 'Cause I had some logic problems with it.
但是你太出彩了 亲爱的
But you sparkled, honey.
他们实在是太喜欢我了 甚至要考虑把原著的男性角色
They liked it so much that they're considering changing the role of Tristan
为了我而改成女的
into a girl just for me.
我为了丽芙着想  必须要阻止她
I had to stop Liv for her own good.
脑残粉太痴狂了
Fanboys are crazy.
我明白这点  因为我也是其中之一
I should know. I'm one of them.
那可是特里斯坦·莱肯啊
We're talking about Tristan Lycanth.
自由世界的捍卫者啊
Keeper of the claw of freedom.
这俩根本就摆不到一起去
Does this match this?
- 你好啊  迪吉  - 你好啊  鲁尼
- What's up, Diggie? - What's up, Rooney?
你的头发怎么了
'Sup with your hair?
你不会只听了我爸啰嗦几句
You did not get a haircut
就把头发理了吧
just because my dad told you to.
不  怎么会
No. Not at all.
我只是觉得头发太长罢了  你认为他会喜欢我的新发型么
I totally needed a trim. Do you think he'll like it?
迪吉  你可不能对他言听计从啊
Diggie, you can't let him push you around like this.
我是说  尽管你之前的头发是一团乱麻
I mean, your hair was a hot mess,
但这不是重点啊
but that's not the point.
我根本控制不住  行不  我想让他喜欢我啊
I can't help it, okay? I want him to like me.
他可是你爸  而我们俩是
He's your dad. And you and me are...
管它是什么呢
Whatever we are.
对啊  管它呢
Totally. Whatever.
呃  你需要找一个
Um... you just need to find something
你和我爸都喜欢的爱好  以此来拉近关系
that you and my dad both like and bond over that.
噢  对  太好了  让我看看
Oh, yeah, okay, great. Let's see.
他喜欢对我大吼大叫
He likes growling at me.
你知道他还喜欢什么吗
You know what else he likes...
烧烤
barbecuing.
烤肉架确实比大嗓门好多了
Grilling sure beats growling.
而且  如果他开始喜欢我了
And, if he starts to like me,
我就可以帮你准备驾照考试了
I could help you prep for your driver's test.
哎呀呀
Aww.
真贴心啊
That's so sweet.
老爸你好啊
Hey, Dad.
我跟你开玩笑呢  亲  哈哈
Dude, I'm kidding. Ha ha.
但他可不会跟你开玩笑
But he won't be.
噢  嘿  丽芙  你想来点巧克力布丁么
Oh! Hey, Liv, you want some chocolate pudding?
我们在冰箱里发现了一大碗
We found a big bowl of it in the fridge.
呃  二位  这可不是巧克力布丁
Um, boys, that's not chocolate pudding.
这是我的从巴黎运来的有机面膜
That's my organic face mask from Paris.
哦  吼吼吼
Oh, ho ho ho.
特制的布丁啊
Fancy pudding.
对  这是用猩猩的大便做出来的
Yeah. It's made with orangutan poop.
这猴子的伙食真是不错啊
Well, whatever that monkey ate was delicious.
我吃了块香蕉么
Is that banana?
好吧  只要
Okay, just...
恶心哟  乔伊
Eww, Joey...
听好了
Get this.
不知道谁在网上散布了小道消息
Somehow word has spread through the blogosphere
说我可能要饰演《太空狼人》里的特里斯坦
that I'm up for the role of Tristan in "Space Werewolves."
我们绝不知道消息是怎么泄露到网上的
Not sure how that info leaked out onto the Internet.
我们怎么会把这么要紧的大新闻发到
We would never post that juicy tidbit
“史蒂文斯波因特《太空狼人》粉丝群”里
on the Stevens Point "Space Werewolves" fan page
来惹毛这帮狼人粉呢
in hopes of enraging local Tristanites.
丽芙到时候会感谢我所做的一切的
Liv will thank me for this later.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你饰演特里斯坦的话  脑残粉们
The fanboys were none too pleased
肯定会把你批判一番的
about you playing Tristan.
你也许要看清形势
You probably want to throw in the towel
知难而退了吧
and back out.
呃  不
Uh, no.
我跟这帮脑子进水的家伙纠结个什么呢
I mean, why do I care what nerd nation
因为我们是一股强大的势力
Because we are a powerful force to be reckoned with...
我是说  他们才是
I mean, they are!
随便吧
Whatever.
这周末我要在纳维尔礼品店店参加
This weekend I have a personal appearance
一个见面会  签售《放声歌唱》的光盘
at Neville's Novelty Shoppe to sign "Sing it Loud!" DVDs.
你们干嘛不跟我来呢
Why don't you guys come with me?
丽芙  纳维尔商店是脑残粉的大本营啊
Liv, Neville's is fanboy central.
如果他们发现你对《太空狼人》的情节一无所知
and then find out that you don't know what you're talking about
就会把你生吞活剥的
they will eat you alive.
这是个生活在太空的狼人故事
He's a werewolf and he lives in space.
我觉得我还需要学习的内容都在这本书里了
I think anything else I need to learn about him will be in here.
我大概周六前就能看完了吧
I can probably finish this by Saturday, yeah?
丽芙  这是第一卷
Liv, that's volume 1.
总共有 64 卷呢
There are 64 volumes.
嗬
Hah!
怪不得他们要把书翻拍成电影
No wonder they're making this into a movie.
谁有工夫看完这么多书啊
Who would want to read all that?
呃
Ugh!
一本交规
323 pages
323 页
of "Rules of the Road,"
而编者只字未提
and not once did they admit
左转进一堆车流里
that turning left into oncoming traffic
是很蠢的
is insane.
420 页的狼人和飞船的故事
420 pages of werewolves and spaceships,
而其中唯一我认真看的就是
and the only thing I'm really looking is that
我穿上特里斯坦的宇航服帅呆了
I think I could totally rock Tristan's space suit.
没错啊
Yeah...
等你看到穆尔斯战役那一段
just wait till they get to the Battle of Mirth.
也就是他遇见凯特拉那段
That's when he meets Kytra,
再后面的历险故事就引人入胜了
and that's when the adventure really kicks off.
你这科幻迷藏得够深啊
You undercover Sci-Fi geek.
你完全就读过这本书
You've totally read this book.
对  我其实全套都看了
Yeah, I've actually read them all.
我很喜欢这书  而且我必须承认
I love them. And I have to admit...
我其实看你去饰演特里斯坦是持观望态度的
I am a little on the fence about you playing Tristan myself.
好吧  其一  你怎敢这么说
Okay... one, how dare you.
其二  帮帮我吧
And two, help me.
得了吧  丽芙  你急个什么呢
Okay, Liv, why are you wigging out?
因为我真的很想要这个角色啊
Because I really want this role.
我知道我已经是个明星了
I mean, I know that I've been playing it cool,
但是参演的这部电影分量最大
but this is way bigger than my show
还能完全把我的演艺事业提升到一片崭新的空间
and it could send me into a completely new acting stratosphere.
但我却不知道怎么给脑残粉留下深刻的印象
I just have no idea how to impress these fanboys.
呃  好吧  我的确很想帮你
Okay, well, I would love to help you
但是  丽芙  我的驾照考试和你的
but, Liv, my driver's test is on the same day
签售会在同一天啊
as your autograph signing.
而我还不知道怎么
And I still have no idea
完成这个愚蠢的左转弯
how to make a stupid left-hand turn.
我有个疯狂的好主意啦
I have a twin-sane idea!
这周六  我就是你而你就是我
This Saturday, I'll be you and you be me.
- 等下  你指的是  - 姐妹身份对调
- Wait, you mean like... - A switch-a-Rooney.
我去摆平这帮脑残粉
I'll face your fanboys.
而你帮我把驾照拿到手
And I will take your driver's test.
太完美了
Perfect!
为什么你的床黏糊糊的
Why is this bed so squishy?
因为我坐在一摊比萨饼上啊
Because I am sitting on a pizza.
体谅一下半夜饿肚子的女孩吧
A girl gets hungry at 3:00 A.M.
这就是我杀死猛龙的全过程
Web... and that's how I slay the dragon.
嘿  亚蒂  你有空么
Hey, Artie, you got a minute?
你好啊  乔伊
Hey, Joey.
你有女朋友啦
You got a girlfriend?
好啊
Burn!
这怎么会好啊  去年秋天你把你妈带到新生舞会上去了
How is that a burn? You took your mom to the freshman dance last fall.
那是什么风把你吹回了
So, what brings you crawling back
学校的太  太  太
to the Society of Space... Space... space...
空  空  空
Were... were... were... Wol... wol... wol...
狼  狼  狼  人  人  社团
wol... wol... wol... ves... ves?
我只是因为觉得戴个狼尾巴很蠢
I was voted out of the Society
就被投票开除了团籍
for suggesting that wolf tails were stupid.
我错了吗
Was I wrong?
同志们  我哪里错了
People, was I wrong?
我想跟你谈谈我姐丽芙的事
I want to talk to you about my sister Liv.
别  啦啦啦我听不见
No la la la la.
我们绝不会说出那个想亵渎特里斯坦的
We do not speak the name of that she-devil
女魔头的名字
who wants to desecrate Tristan.
除非她委托你来请我陪她跳舞
Unless she sent you to ask me to prom,
这样的话  跟她说我也许会答应
in which case, let her know I say maybe.
不见不散了
Be gone with you.
听好了  亚蒂
Listen, Artie.
我们有个公敌啊
We have a common enemy here,
我们必须通力合作
and we need to work together
来保证特里斯坦的神圣地位
to defend the iconic character
不可被撼动
that is Tristan.
你我原本是强有力的同盟
We were once powerful allies, you and I.
磕碰不断的盟友啊
An uneasy alliance.
我的狼耳朵竖起来了
My wolf ears are perked.
丽芙明天会到纳维尔商店
Liv will be down at Neville's tomorrow.
我要让你给她秀秀《太空狼人》
I need you to show her the real fangs
脑残粉真正的獠牙
of a true "Space Werewolves" fanboy.
脑残粉
Fanboy?
这可是个贬义词啊  同志
That term is derogatory, sir.
我们更喜欢被称作“空想主义爱好者”
We prefer "fantasy enthusiast."
所以你要去砸场子
So will you do it?
哦  听起来爽极了  乔伊
Oh, sounds great, Joey.
我会高兴地跳着舞钻进你的圈套里啊
I'd happily waltz right into your trap.
你把我当傻瓜了吗
Do you take me for a fool?!
是的  我确实把你当傻瓜了
Yes. Yes, I do.
而换做特里斯坦的话就是
But as Tristan himself would say...
当你的敌人
When an enemy
伸出了魔爪  舔一口吧
offers his  paw, lick it.
若你可在明日将他的后腿
If only to tear off his hind leg...
碎成万段
Tomorrow.
哦
Oh!
不去踢馆子就像是
Saying no to that would be like
背叛了特里斯坦一样
saying no to Tristan himself.
干得漂亮  孤狼
Well played, lone wolf.
干得够漂亮
Well played indeed.
啊
Aah!
傻缺
Nerds!
聊天发短信请靠边
Pull over to talk or text.
唔  这块红糖烧肉真是太好吃了
Mmm! Gotta love a brown sugar glaze.
走廊内严禁饮食
No eating in the halls.
我忍不住啊  教练
I can't help it, coach.
这肉真叫入口即化
Just falls off the bone.
你拿的好像是上等的烤牛排啊
That's some solid-looking barbecue you got there.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是看《烧烤月刊》上的步骤做的
I followed a recipe from "Barbecue Monthly."
哎呀  黑胡椒放多了
Oh! Too much black pepper.
烧烤真是一门高深的艺术啊
Ah, it was all so confusing.
我爸爸是个
My father's...
素食主义者
A vegetarian.
我一直缺少一位烧烤方面的导师
I just have no one to guide me.
呃  不是我故意炫耀
Well, I don't like to brag,
但是去年夏天我确实在
but last summer I did win
史蒂文斯波因特烧烤比赛中拔得头筹
the Stevens Point "Thrilla on the Grilla" cook-off.
太棒了  鲁尼教练果然吃了烧烤这一套
Oh, yeah! Coach Rooney took the barbecue bait.
但是为什么他对我的发型只字未提
But seriously, not one word about the haircut?
这不是白弄了么
What gives?
嘿 快看啊
Hey, check it out...
我刚把丽芙的牙刷卖给了《放声歌唱》的粉丝
I sold Liv's toothbrush to a "Sing it Loud!" Fan
得到了一堆黏糊糊的眼球糖
and got us a bunch of gummy eyeballs.
真可惜  她只有一把牙刷
Too bad she only has one toothbrush.
哦  开玩笑呢吧  那把牙刷是我在人行道边上捡的
Oh, please... I picked that one off the sidewalk out front.
呃
Oh...
姐妹身份对调开始了
The switch-a-Rooney was on.
我花了四个小时来烫头发
It took me four hours to do my hair
而且丽芙要让我把头晾在床外睡觉
and Liv made me sleep with my head hanging off the mattress
来确保不把头发给压回去了
to protect the pouf.
我的口水甚至流到我鼻子里了
I drooled into my own nose.
非常感谢各位光临
Thank you all so much for coming
第四季的《放声歌唱》
to the season 4 DVD signing
光盘签售会
of  Sing it Loud!
亚蒂来了
Artie's here.
好戏开场了
Let the games begin.
丽芙·鲁尼
Liv Rooney.
近日有流言说你
Are the rumors true that you,
一个黄毛丫头  要饰演特里斯坦·莱肯
a girl, might play Tristan Lycanth?
流言是真的  脑残粉
It's true, fanboy.
你还有意见了
What say you?
我的意见是这是罪恶滔天不可饶恕的
I say it's intergalactic blasphemy!
而我会证明你根本不值得演这个角色
And I shall prove you're unworthy.
注意一下  我的小喽啰们在网络直播呢
Be warned my minions are live blogging.
网址是  伟大的亚蒂王@狼圈.嗷呜
King_Artie_the_magnificent @ wolfspot dot howl.
哈哈
Ha ha.
放马过来吧  亚蒂王
Bring it on, king Artie.
说说特里斯坦的血统吧
Speak for Tristan's lineage.
他的父母是谁
Who are his parents?
丽芙马上要出大丑啦
Liv is about to go down in flames.
他的父母
His parents
是狼人马格洛
are the werewolf Magrol
和赛拉女王
and queen Zira.
哈  咋样
Bam! What?!
我是说  真是个妙绝了的好问题啊
I mean, space-tastic question.
原来是玛蒂
Maddie.
好啦  咱们可以上路了
Okay, we are good to go.
呃  你好像忘了一件事情嘛
Uh, I think we're forgetting one thing.
哦  对  对
Oh! Ha ha. Yes.
还没有涂唇彩呢
Lip gloss.
不  记录上写着你必须戴着眼镜
No, it says here you're required to wear glasses
才能开车
to drive.
是吗
Does it say that?
我只是拍照的时候会戴眼镜的
I thought I just needed those for the picture.
给我戴上你的眼镜
Put 'em on.
哦  天哪  我的眼睛
O. M. Eyeballs.
发动  换挡
Now start the car and put it in gear.
当然
Absolutely. ( Laughs )
如果您能  告诉我
If you could just... Direct me to the...
点火器在哪里
Ignition.
好像不能是吧
No?
启动了  很好
All right. This is good.
左转  前面有建筑物
Now merge left. There's construction ahead.
- 呃  - 左转  左转啊
- Uh... - Go left. I said left!
太快了太快了
Okay, too far, too far.
- 明白  - 垃圾桶
- Okay. - Garbage can.
我不知道
I don't...
现在
Okay.
停车
Pull the vehicle over.
呃  好的
Uh, uh, okay.
减速  减速
Slow down. Slow down!
- 我不  - 邮箱
- I'm not... I... - Mailbox.
- 邮箱啊  - 你在说啥
- Mailbox! - What?!
这样的话
So...
我过了吗
Pass?
好咧  咱俩哥们
Here we are... a couple of dudes
要来点烧烤乐子了
getting ready to do some chillin' and grillin'.
我刚刚叫你哥们没问题吧
Are you okay that I just called you a dude?
放松放松哥们  我们是在烧烤
Relax, we're barbecuing.
烧烤的时候  大家都是哥们
Everybody's a dude.
太好了  正式行动啦
Okay. Let's do this.
当然咯
Absolutely.
不过  首先  我要你办点事儿
First, I need you to do a few things.
悉听尊便
Hit me. Whatever you want.
剥玉米  给肉入味
Shuck the corn? Season the meat?
修草坪
Mow the lawn.
呃  啥
Um, what?
清水管  换轮胎
And clean the gutters, rotate my tires,
补浴盆  还有洗碗
grout the tub, and empty the dishwasher.
哥们
Dude.
这些都跟烧烤八竿子打不到一块儿啊
What does that have to do with barbecuing?
我怎么就真以为你来我这儿是学东西的呢
I thought you came here to learn.
我先去修草坪
Let me go get the lawn mower.
我知道迪吉的伎俩
I knew exactly what Diggie was doing.
借烧烤之名来拉拢我这个老爸
Using barbecue to soften up the old man?
他要是想博得我的好感
If he wanted to get on my good side,
还是得先
he was going to have to get on the good side
过了日常家务这一关再说
of my to-do list.
终于  有甜头了
Finally, a little thrilla on the grilla!
家务活儿饿死人
All those chores made me hungry.
这是我的
That's mine.
怎么  你竟然忘记带你自己的牛排来了
What... did you forget to bring your own steak?
下次咯
Maybe next time.
下次
Next time?
我成功啦
I'm in! ( Laughs )
噢
Aah!
带你自己的牛排来  太经典了
"Bring your own steak." Classic!
你为什么要折磨那个可怜的孩子
Why are you messing with that poor boy?
只是确认一下他配不配得上咱们女儿
I'm just making sure he's good enough for my daughter.
真是辛苦的一天啊
And I'm done for the day.
别告诉玛蒂
Don't tell Maddie,
不过话说回来  除了他那搞笑的名字
but except for that stupid name,
迪吉那男孩其实不错
Diggie's all right.
最后一个问题
Final question, girl.
特里斯坦劈开宇宙太虚的时候
When Tristan split the galactic pangaea,
他跟那里的原住民说了什么
what did he say to the scattering colonies?
狼人们  迁居他星吧
"Run to the stars, wolves.
但是永远以你们的家人为重
But always put first your families.
因为  正是他们的爱
For their love
你们才会出现在宇宙
keeps you tethered to the universe."
哇  你还必须得承认
Wow. You've gotta admit...
玛蒂真心保住了丽芙的面子啊
Maddie's making Liv look really good.
她骗不了任何人
She's not fooling anyone.
却骗了这里的所有人
Well, except everyone here.
哇  丽芙鲁尼
Well, Liv Rooney...
你通过了
I'm sold.
我是说  你演特里斯坦会很棒的
I mean, you will make a great Tristan Lycanth.
向特里斯坦小姐致礼
All hail the she-Tristan!
呃  知会一声
And, FYI...
我舞会还没邀请别人
I currently am available for le prom.
但是好像你
But your window of opportunity
没有机会啦
is closing.
邦
Boop!
亚蒂
Artie.
你好好想想
Are you serious?
你真能接受我姐姐出演崔特里斯坦吗
You can accept my sister playing Tristan?
你还有什么
What part of...
想不通的  哈
Don't you understand?
这么说  帕克和我是最后
Okay, so Parker and I are the only ones
持干戈之矛的人咯
that have a problem with this?
呃  话说回来
Um, speak for yourself.
丽芙也得我心
She won me over too.
亚蒂  给我来条尾巴
Artie, tail me.
直到此刻  我才意识到
It was at that moment that I realized
我才是可能会伤害丽芙的
I was the crazy fanboy
那个脑残粉
that I was trying to protect Liv from.
我才是被家族逐弃的人
I was untethered from my family.
我才是离群之狼
I was the lone wolf.
并且  我不该吃那 15 个泡泡眼球糖的
And I should not have eaten 15 gummy eyeballs.
亚蒂
You know what, Artie...
我也要一条尾巴
tail me too.
向特里斯坦小姐致礼
All hail the she-Tristan!
让我把这件事情说说清楚
Let me make one thing clear.
你们两个这是最后一次对调身份
This was the last switch-a-Rooney.
你们六岁那年这么折腾过一次
You did it when you were 6.
然后我在你们两个额头上都
And I wrote your names on your forehead
拿记号笔写了你们的名字
in permanent marker.
你们别逼我再这么来一次
Don't make me do that again.
对哦  发箍之夏
Ah, yes... the summer of headbands.
话说回来  我们当时的发箍造型都不错呢
To be fair, though, we rocked the headband look.
哈  哈  有趣
Ha ha fun fun.
玛蒂  你 17 岁之前不允许考驾照
Maddie, no license till you're 17.
看你这个造型怎么拗
Rock that look.
17 岁  真的
17?! Seriously?
莫非你想等到 18 岁再说
You want to make it 18?
啊  17 岁啊  等不及了
Ah, 17. Looking forward to it.
还有  丽芙
And Liv,
既然你这么喜欢开车
since you like driving so much,
在我通知你之前你是我的私人司机
you are now my personal chauffeur until further notice.
- 不要啊  - 没错
- No! - Yes.
万事不算小  万里不称遥
There is no errand too small, no trip too far.
或许我只是出门拿个报纸
I might even have you take me down to the end of the driveway
也会要你开车载我
just to get the newspaper.
我不知道你们怎么看
I don't know.
没错  孩子们
That's right, girls.
我刚刚投下了一个巨型老妈弹
I just dropped an atomic mom bomb.
嘭
Boom!
她这话不当真吧
She can't be serious about that, right?
我们真的到现在还
Do we seriously still get newspapers
有订报纸上门
delivered to our house?
不过你在纳威店里表现不错
Hey, whatever you did down at Neville's totally worked.
有个叫孤狼粉丝发起了联署
Some fanboy named lone wolf started a petition
想要片方让我出演特里斯坦
to get me the role of Tristan.
你成功的说服了粉丝们
You won over the fanboys.
谢谢了
Thank you.
我能确定孤狼就是乔伊
Pretty sure lone wolf is actually lone Joey.
你应该去谢谢他的
You should go thank him.
等等  我记得你不是说乔伊
Wait, I thought you said that Joey
是哪个想要破坏我们的人么
was the one trying to sabotage us.
这事说来话长啊
It was a long and complicated day.
了解
Got it.
还有  很抱歉我搞砸了你的驾照考试
Also I'm sorry about wrecking your driver's test.
真的砸了  哈
Literally. Ha!
我给你带来了一个纪念品
And I got you something.
你应该把这个去还给胡佛家
You might want to return this to the... hoovers.
谢了
Thanks.
想起来了
That reminds me.
我也有个东西要给你
I got you something as well.
亚蒂的狼尾巴
One of Artie's wolf tails. Yeah.
哦  还有  你今年舞会有舞伴了
Oh! Also I got you a date to the prom.
对哦
Yeah.
亚蒂想知道你到时候打算穿什么
Artie would like to know what kind of dress
你是打算穿法师装  还是飞马装
you will be wearing... Wizard or Pegasus?
丽芙  你这话可没错
Liv, you were absolutely right.
我从来没想到这么坐在副驾驶座
It is mind-blowing what I can accomplish
我能完成多少事情
from the passenger seat of the car.
我付了账单  订了几件漂亮衣服
I paid a bill, ordered some cute tops,
领养了只企鹅
and adopted a penguin.
唔  有短信
Ooh! Incoming.
哦
Oh!
啊
Aah!
这好好笑
That's funny.
玛蒂刚发来一张好搞笑的照片
Maddie just sent me the funniest photo.
- 你们两个小子想看看么  - 好啊  好啊  好啊
- You boys want to see it? - Yeah. Yeah yeah.
好的  我这就转发
Okay, I'll send.
这才叫经典啊
That's classic!
各位都在笑什么呢
What is everybody laughing at?
各位都在看什么呢  什么东西这么搞笑呢
What are we looking at? What's so funny?
我不喜欢开车
I hate driving!